[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Hello, everyone.
I'm Yu Meng.
(Snackable content, OOTD) Welcome, everyone.
(The wealthy only girl, Lucky woman) Welcome to Rongmei Rising Stars Review.
Next up, we have
a rising star
from Rongmei Media,
(Trophy wife) who dominates the relationship niche,
(Jiali Cosmetics' biggest fan) known for her "trophy wife" persona.
Lucky Beauty Yu,
Yu Meng.
(Toilet)
(These past few days,)
(I've been having a really, really tough time.)
First,
I owe my colleagues
an apology.
I didn't mean
to leave suddenly today.
But please believe me,
if one day
I vanish from the public eye,
it must be because of
my husband,
Di Liren.
♪Neon lights twist into a knot♪
♪I rest in the ruins of defeat♪
♪You tap your fingers lightly♪
♪I fall into the abyss♪
♪I've seen this game before♪
♪Every single move was calculated♪
♪I finally see your silhouette♪
♪Just an empty shell♪
♪I've broken this game before♪
♪Every move was placed wrong♪
♪Now it's my turn to play♪
♪I'll show you what stunning looks like♪
♪When I stand back up again♪
♪The whole city goes dark♪
♪For the part you owe me♪
♪I'll make you pay double♪
♪You're just my starting point♪
=The Vanishing Beauty=
=Episode 1=
(One month ago)
Happy fifth wedding anniversary!
♪I don't need anyone to prove how special I am♪
♪Even my flaws sparkle♪
Honey,
aren't you afraid of heights?
I want to overcome my fear,
so I can do what you love
and explore the world
with you.
Honey.
Right now, in my heart,
you're the coolest guy in Jiangzhou.
Adjust altitude
according to the wind direction.
♪I never fail♪
♪Every choice brings me closer to♪
Down there.
♪Lucky♪
♪I don't need the world to define how special I am♪
It's so beautiful, Honey!
I love you.
I love you too.
♪Even the wind is enchanted by me♪
♪Even a wrong step turns into an iconic scene♪
♪Even my meltdowns have my tone♪
♪Lucky♪
Okay, look here.
One more shot.
Like overlooking
the city from above?
But I prefer you
changing yourself for me.
♪I never give up♪
♪Every choice brings me closer to♪
♪A miracle♪
Are you okay?
Will we
get to see each other again?
(If someone had told me a few days ago)
(that I'd meet)
(a wonderful girl,)
even if it were
just a brief encounter,
(Honey, Happy fifth anniversary) and we'd never meet again,
(I think)
(I would make the same choice.)
Meng, trust me.
I will find a way
to earn your dad's approval.
I'll take care of you.
Honey.
The day I met you,
I used up all my luck.
Five years ago, I told you
I didn't have money,
but one day, I'd get you
a bigger diamond ring.
And today
is the day.
These five years,
I work harder
than the day before.
I want you to be happy,
so you won't regret choosing me.
And I love you
more than I did five years ago.
(A lovestruck brain)
(is a man's best dowry.)
(I just want)
(his wholehearted devotion.)
(And he delivers.)
(Someone asked me)
(what "a lucky woman" means.)
(I would say)
(it's a woman who marries the right person)
(and spends life)
(with him at a leisurely pace.)
(Lucky Beauty Yu)
(Wanderer: Put Mr. Di on the cart)
(Passerby A: Put the link up! I'm buying it!)
(VIP Player has joined the live stream)
(Starry Sky: Why isn't the link up yet?) Thank you all for the best wishes.
(Smile at Starlight: I want Mr. Di) I'm so happy to share
my joy with you.
(lvresre: You trophy wife)
Couples who show off break up fast.
(lvresre: Couples who show off break up fast)
(Starry Sky: I don't get that kind of man) Who's "Couples who show off"?
(Blue Sky: PDA makes you break up fast) Could that be you, buddy?
(For: If it were me, I'd even laugh in my sleep)
(Nine Miles Same: Rich girls are hard to please)
How to guarantee
(Looking Forward:) your husband's loyalty?
(Lycheein: Happy) He might have cheated on you already.
(Smile at Starlight: Envy) Then you can seduce him.
(Sweet Tea: Good evening!)
(Sweetheart: Envying others' love again) I mean it.
(Looking Forward: I don't envy the rich) If you can seduce my husband,
(I only envy the one who have Mr. Di) then I'll give in.
(Mochi: Lucky Beauty Yu is excellent, beautiful and capable)
(VIP Player: I heard Mr. Di built his fortune off his wife)
(Conquer the World: Can't handle it) Chen Chen.
(VIP Player: My tears aren't worth much, but I'm crying sincerely)
(Nine Miles Same: Please, just give me a chance to place an order)
(I'm afraid it won't be available)
(Mr. Di: Limited, sold out)
(Past Youth: Good)
(ZzzZ: I'm here to support you!)
(Blue Sky: He only exists in novels) If you manage to seduce him,
(and is mass-produced in my dreams) then I'll hand this bouquet
(Passerby A: Do you need a sister?) to you myself
(Homebody Cat: Put him on the link,) and count it as your win.
(or it'd be the ultimate disrespect to consumers)
(Promise: I really like it)
(Live stream ended)
What's going on?
Got cut off again.
Zi, what's going on?
(Zi)
(You got reported.)
(Can't you change)
(your habit)
(of talking back?)
They can insult me,
so why can't I talk back?
Got cut off again?
So annoying.
How could they?
There's a card here.
(Princess, please accept the flowers)
(May these flowers fill you with joy, may your days be gentle and bright.)
Honey.
The person in this photo
looks a lot like you.
Let me see.
It really is me.
Chen Chen.
Check what's this about.
Mr. Di.
Last week,
we negotiated
with the supplier.
You got drunk,
and I took you to the hotel.
No idea who took it.
Zhang Tao.
Look into it.
Find out who did this.
Got it.
Go ahead.
Tell me once you find out.
But I'm keeping these photos.
This is my golden opportunity
to blackmail you.
As you wish.
Lost again.
Have a rest.
Here you go.
Where are you aiming at?
Pick it up.
Honey?
Honey.
Why coming here?
What about the event?
I finished it early today,
so I come
to play for fun with Zi.
Zi,
you go rest over there.
I need to talk to Liren.
Honey.
I just remembered
the photos you saw last time
was likely taken last week.
Don't misunderstand.
Let me tell you.
Chen was with Mr. Han that day.
I was just covering for him,
and doing him a favor.
I know.
Honey,
how long have you been practicing here?
All told,
it's been five months.
Mr. Han has been cooperating
with us.
I want to negotiate
a new project contract with him.
But he hasn't given me the chance.
Lately he's gotten into tennis
and hiking.
He signed me up
for next month's marathon.
What can I do?
I have to go along with it.
No wonder you've been
morning jogging lately.
Meng.
Long time no see.
Long time no see, Mr. Han.
Liren told me
he'd be meeting
an important friend today
and insisted I come.
But I had an event earlier,
and got delayed a bit.
So I'm late.
It's okay.
Let me introduce
our company's PR director,
also my sister-in-law, Weng Yue.
Yu Meng.
Hello, Miss Weng.
I've seen your posts.
Lucky Beauty Yu.
With many followers.
Not really.
Just sharing my life.
No nutritional value indeed.
So Miss Weng,
you're studying nutrition?
You can even tell
if my account has nutritional value.
Actually, I do enjoy watching
short videos.
It's a trend.
How many followers now?
Over a million?
Relied on Dad as a kid,
and relies on husband now.
People just
find it novel.
Miss Weng knows me so well.
She knows everything.
That means my life
is quite interesting,
or why would you
know me so well?
Not at all.
I don't know you.
But I know trophy wives well.
My sister is one.
Usually she doesn't come to the office.
But when she shows up,
people have to praise her
for being amazing and capable.
What a tough life, Mr. Di.
But you can't take a part for the whole.
You can't assume everyone else
is like your sister.
Miss Weng,
you should
broaden your perspective.
Mr. Han,
my wife Meng
plays tennis really well.
She taught me how to play.
Perfect, let's play a match.
If you win,
for the new contract,
I'll give another 0.5 percent concession.
If you lose,
you give me another 0.5 percent.
Deal?
Since Mr. Han proposed it,
how about
we round it up?
One percent.
How's it?
Deal.
Check please.
Court three.
Booked by Mr. Di.
Okay, just a moment.
Will Mr. Han back out
on the concession he promised?
Don't take it seriously.
He was just saying that.
Then why did you go all out just now?
Han Guang didn't budge.
The contract isn't finalized.
How did he know
how much one percent is?
He didn't want to make the concession,
but wanted me to see
that in the partnership
between Jiali and him,
he holds the upper hand.
That's all.
You are so sharp
when it comes to business,
but about Di Liren,
why do you believe everything?
You saw it.
Liren and that Chen Chen
have nothing going on.
He was just covering for Han Guang.
Please scan here to pay.
Right.
Should I give Mr. Di's new membership gift
to you now,
or to Mr. Di
next time?
New membership?
(How long have you been practicing here?)
(All told,)
(it's been five months.)
What's wrong?
Weng Yue?
No wonder she's so hostile towards you.
Case solved.
(You always say you're lucky.)
(My luck isn't as good as yours.)
I haven't met
someone outstanding like Mr. Di.
(But he works too hard.)
(If it were me,)
(I could've helped him more.)
(Weng Yue)
(Yaoyan Daily Chemicals, Weng Yue)
(Mr. Di, available this afternoon? Let's discuss future collaboration.)
(Time and place.)
(Run because I don't want to run.)
(This workout improves aerobic capacity, high intensity)
Honey, what are you looking at?
Stop it.
Honey.
You have a call.
Hello?
Go ahead.
There are comments online
questioning your body fat rate.
I'll take a picture
and show them all.
Okay, no problem.
(New semester, new journey)
You suspect
your husband
started morning jogs
because of Weng Yue?
I'm not suspecting my husband.
I'm worried that another woman
is eyeing him.
What's the difference?
Of course there's a difference.
Right.
I got the workout data
from his phone and his watch.
Take a look for me.
Mom!
Liu Bai,
my brother.
You should go to him.
He studied psychology,
a fan of detective novels and crime shows.
He had been unemployed for three years.
He just came recently
to live with me.
Feel free to bother him. Don't be shy.
Hello, Meng.
Bai.
Ms. Meng.
Mom.
They're always playing tennis
together.
As emotions rise,
they might touch each other.
What if Weng Yue
can't resist
my husband's charm,
and wants to be the mistress?
Let's call her "Missy".
If Weng Yue
is the one who gave you the photos,
she's either already a "Missy",
or on her way to becoming one.
(Honey, I have a lot of work to do today.)
(I won't be home till late.)
(Can't have dinner with you.)
(Let Liu Zi eat with you.)
(Weng Yue's moments) I'm all ready.
We'll meet later.
I'm feeling excited and nervous.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Where are you going?
For something big.
The scent of this lip gloss
is way too strong.
Besides citrus notes, there are also
weird smells like
vanilla,
coffee,
and fried rice?
(Jiali)
A false alarm
is the most beautiful word
in the world.
Let's go, Zi.
Grab a drink.
Booked. See you at the usual place.
Okay.
Thanks.
You ordered alcohol?
Aren't you trying
for a baby?
But I ordered so many snacks.
If we can't finish them,
it'll be a waste.
Thanks.
Wasting food is a sin.
You told your fans
you've been sticking to
the 16:8 diet.
Exactly.
Sixteen hours of eating,
eight hours of fasting.
Isn't that the 16:8 diet?
Come on, cheers.
Fine.
Your husband is indeed having a meeting.
But there are questions
unresolved.
Who exactly slipped the photos
into the flowers?
What's the aim?
And he just got
a new tennis membership card.
Why did he say
he's been playing for months?
I think
it's just a misunderstanding.
Think about it.
He loves me so much.
How could he lie to me?
What a classic trophy wife quote.
Besides,
he's had Zhang Tao investigate,
but no lead yet.
We don't know
where the problem lies.
As for the membership card...
I've realized now
trying to wake up a trophy wife
is like convincing a man to give up
having children.
But Zi,
why do I feel
so uneasy?
Don't be uneasy.
Maybe we're overthinking.
After all, Di Liren
passed through your family's
(Good product share, Lucky Beauty Yu) all sorts of tests
to marry you.
(Honey says I'm younger year after year) And his current career
is built entirely on your dad's foundation.
He wouldn't dare act rashly.
Definitely.
Exactly.
You're right.
If you question him again,
you're questioning me.
Right?
Right.
(Miss Yu, there are rumors about Mr. Di) I don't trust men,
(If you want to know, DM me) but I trust you.
(What? Don't tell me it's that thing)
Even though I misunderstood him today,
he has to apologize to me.
How about this?
I'll give him a chance.
Let him come pick me up,
giving him an out.
(Happy)
(Liu Bai) It's my brother.
I'll take it.
Okay.
Everybody,
all eyes on me!
Look over here!
Miss Yu, thank you
for ordering a bottle of Black Ace!
(Classy)
(Honey)
Why hasn't he asked me
what I'm doing at the bar?
Can't you see my post?
(Credit card charge: 3,000 yuan Transaction completed)
Why isn't anyone coming to pick me up?
Miss Yu.
Can we talk a bit?
Honey, you finally came to get me.
Let's go.
You've had too much.
I'll sober you up.
Come on.
Where are we going?
Watch the steps.
Zi.
- I compared the workout data - Hello?
on Di Liren's phone and watch.
What do you mean?
Something's off.
Some data don't match.
It could be
a network signal issue.
But either way,
none of the data has anything
to do with Weng Yue.
You talk to Meng
directly.
I feel so dizzy.
Where am I?
I want to puke.
Where's Zi?
Where's my phone?
I need to call her.
I need to make a call.
Give me my phone back.
Come on.
I'm going to puke.
I feel bad.
Just take a rest.
Okay?
Rest a bit.
I feel so sick.
Why isn't this elevator opening?
That's the door.
I know it's the door.
Think I need you to tell me?
Could you check me in?
Here.
Take a photo.
You
use my phone.
I'll take a couple for you.
Come on, pose.
Ready.
Here, done.
Check it.
Looks good.
Thank you.
Why does this hotel
keep
spinning and spinning?
It's making me so dizzy.
That's because you're drunk.
Let's go.
Take a rest.
Come.
Wait!
Don't touch me.
Or I'll call the police.
Who are you?
Think of me
as a friend.
I like making friends.
And
I know a lot of people like you.
You all have a friend
who's been hurt by marriage.
I listen to their stories
and help them move on.
What about you?
Maybe I can help with
your troubles.
Troubles?
I have no troubles.
My husband
loves me very much.
And my marriage is perfect.
You can leave.
I have no troubles.
Then why isn't he here?
That's because...
Because...
Don't you wonder
why he isn't taking your calls?
Where is he right now?
None of your business!
He's my husband,
not yours.
Right.
Why hasn't he
come pick me up?
Why is no one coming for me?
Where's my husband?
This is the problem
I solve best.
It's my expertise.
Can you keep this
secret?
I...
Because I'm an influencer.
I have
20 million followers online.
Promise to keep it secret.
Alright.
Keep it secret.
Let's go now.
(Zi: 20 Missed Calls)
(Zi.)
(Don't worry.)
(I'm fine.)
Here's your breakfast.
You brought me
here last night?
You passed out in a booth alone,
and your friend ditched you.
I took you here
out of worry.
Out of worry?
If you were really worried,
you'd take me
to the police station.
Tell me, how much do you want?
Name your price.
WeChat Pay or Alipay?
I think
I should reintroduce myself.
I'm Jiao Xu.
I'm
a divorce lawyer.
A divorce lawyer?
(Jiao Xu Lawyer)
(Yihe Firm) I don't break up couples,
but give them a graceful exit.
Are you lawyers
getting so desperate?
Soliciting clients at bars?
No choice.
I am
a professional divorce lawyer.
Sensing a woman's urge
to get a divorce
is as simple as a cheetah
smelling its prey.
So your sensing failed you.
I'm so sorry.
I don't want a divorce.
Ms. Yu,
I can offer you
a free service.
There's a trick scumbags love to use.
I call it setting up a straw man.
He'll make you
accuse him of cheating,
let you make a scene,
and push things to their peak.
Then, he'd play the victim,
showing evidence
to prove his innocence.
Burdened with guilt
for wronging him,
when that scumbag
shows signs of infidelity,
you wouldn't dare look into it.
Instead, you'll doubt yourself,
afraid of wronging him again.
That's exactly
what he wants.
Mr. Jiao,
do you really think
that eavesdropping on people
makes you impressive?
Ms. Yu,
do you really think
suspicion
pops out of thin air?
You know so much about scumbags.
Are you one yourself?
No need to be so hostile.
I,
as a lawyer,
specialize in divorce cases.
All my clients are women.
I'm very experienced.
Fine, whatever.
Save it.
Even if I needed a lawyer,
I'd never hire you.
(I'm Jiao Xu.)
Call me for your divorce.
By the way,
you need to find out the mistress.
(Jiao Xu) Words can lie,
but scents never do.
(Professionalism brings honor, responsibility outweighs honor)
(Jiao Xu, A Distinguished Lawyer)
He really is a lawyer.
Honey.
You didn't pick me up last night,
and you're leaving early.
Where are you going?
I was just going to pick you up.
I made you some hot soup.
I'm sorry, Honey.
We had a meeting
that ran late yesterday.
Once I saw your text,
I called you right back.
But Liu Zi told me
you were already asleep.
Told me not to wake you.
Have some warm soup.
But no matter how busy you were,
you'd be on call 24/7,
waiting for my messages.
Jinghua is about to go public,
so the company is swamped.
I've been overwhelmed.
Honey,
I promise
I'll never make you
wait again.
Okay?
Again?
If it happens again, you're dead.
I guarantee.
Right.
My staff said
you left your lipstick at the office.
Look.
But
how would they know
this is mine?
When I went to the restroom,
I didn't see anyone there.
This is
the limited edition for you.
Other female employees
can't get one of this.
Someone used it.
When I put on lipstick,
I only ever slant it to one side.
But look at this now.
Someone clearly used it.
That's out of line!
If someone used
my things,
I don't want them anymore.
Honey,
don't worry.
Tomorrow,
I'll lay down the rules.
No one dares do it again.
It feels off.
Something's wrong.
What's wrong?
The hash brown.
I can tell
it's been frozen forever.
It tastes awful.
That's all I have in the fridge.
Just make do for now.
You said
Liu Bai told you
the data on Liren's phone
and his watch don't match.
He tells you he's jogging every morning,
but he's going somewhere else.
Where could he be going?
If you really want to find out,
Liu Bai has a way.
Meng.
If we
do this just based on one photo,
and Liren finds out,
no matter how,
it'll ruin your relationship.
You're right.
We only have this photo.
Do it!
(He's out.)
(Zi:)
(Okay.)
(Underground Parking)
(Lakeside Spring)
I'm sorry, Bai.
I didn't mean to.
It's fine.
Take it easy.
I was thinking
I don't know anyone
living at Lakeside Spring.
Seeing Zhang Tao made me realize
Di Liren
faked his jog.
Zhang Tao
wears Di Liren's watch,
which explains why
the data
don't match.
Looks like Di Liren
is pretty good at covering his tracks.
However, he still can't escape
your scrutiny.
Your brother is nothing like you.
He's such a pushover.
He's with Dad,
and I am with Mom.
B-But I did see
Di Liren buzzed the intercom
at a building.
I couldn't see the unit number,
but I heard
a woman's voice asking,
"Didn't you bring your key?"
He said he forgot.
A woman?
He faked his jog
and lied to you.
You think that was some client?
I asked
Meng
to check with
the CFO about
Zhang Tao's recent parking expense claims.
I found two clues.
First,
the car he drove
to Lakeside Spring
wasn't the one
you had me check.
But that car
is under his name.
It's a new car he bought.
I've never seen it before.
Second,
every morning, this car picks someone up
at Lakeside Spring
and heads to Jiali Cosmetics.
In the evening,
it leaves Jiali Cosmetics
and goes back to Lakeside Spring.
The woman works at Jiali.
Right under your nose.
You haven't been involved with
the company much,
so you didn't notice it.
But even if you
did notice something,
Di Liren could easily
fool you.
That's true.
Thinking back now,
except for Mr. Dong who's been close to me
and is still the CFO,
all the other positions
have been completely reshuffled.
I barely know anyone now.
Then find a way
to get to know them.
I have an idea.
Honey,
I'd like to host
a barbecue party.
What do you think?
First,
to treat the staff.
Second,
to thank you for the anniversary surprise.
You can't cook.
Host it at a restaurant,
okay?
That won't do.
It's so insincere.
No, I'll host it at home.
It's a great chance to win over your team.
Don't worry,
I'll let everyone
enjoy themselves.
I'm worried you'll be exhausted.
I won't.
Besides,
we have Ms. Hui.
She can cook, and I'll assist.
Mom and Dad need
Ms. Hui too.
Well,
I'll hire someone to help out.
Why do you reject
everything I say?
Whatever.
I only trust Ms. Hui.
Honey,
I want to discuss something
with you.
Just the two of us
are in a house this big.
Ms. Hui and Mr. Sun
come over every few days to clean
and tend the garden.
It is really inconvenient.
I think
we should hire our own
housekeeper and gardener,
so we don't need
to borrow them from your parents.
Do you agree?
I said no!
If this isn't
the life you want,
you can stick
to your own ideas.
Don't always go along with me.
Or you'll feel resentful.
This is my own choice.
We live with our own choices.
(You must be Ms. Yu Meng.)
(Ms. Liu Zi has already)
(booked for you.)
I want something distinct
and long-lasting.
(These are too ordinary.)
(No different from mainstream perfumes.)
(Is there anything more special?)
(I want a perfume)
(I could recognize instantly.)
(Sorry.)
(You might be allergic)
(to this plant extract.)
I want this one.
Hello, Mrs. Di.
Hello.
(Citrus Perfume)
Hello, Mrs. Di.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to the party.
(Iris Perfume) Enjoy yourselves.
(Amber Perfume) Have fun.
- Will do. Thanks, Mrs. Di. - Thanks, Mrs. Di.
Mrs. Di.
(Rose Perfume) Hello.
- Hello, Mrs. Di. - Hello, Mrs. Di. Hello!
- Hello, Mrs. Di. - Hi, Mrs. Di!
All these desserts
were made by me.
(Tuberose EDT, Cedar Perfume) Eat up.
Thanks.
- Have fun. - Thanks, Mrs. Di.
- Thanks, Mrs. Di. - Thank you!
(Sandalwood Perfume) Have fun.
(Lily of the Valley Perfume) - Thanks, Mrs. Di. - Have fun.
Her name is Gao Shan.
(Gao Shan, Brand Director of Jiali) She's the Brand Director of Jiali,
in charge of marketing.
She and her husband
are going strong.
It's probably not her.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Luo Ye) She is Luo Ye,
(E-commerce Director of Jiali) the E-commerce Director of Jiali,
highly capable.
(Except for essential work communication,)
- (she barely socializes with anyone.) - Welcome. - Mrs. Di,
when will you come back?
(Lavender EDT) I really miss the time
(Vetiver Perfume) working with you.
I'm in no rush to go back.
With you all here, I'm at ease.
Rourou, you're here.
(She is Zhang Yu,)
(the Product Director of Jiali,)
(hailed as the closest thing)
(to an AI work machine)
(in the company.)
I heard Liren really appreciates her
(Zhang Yu, Product Director of Jiali)
and relies on her input
for projects.
Hello, Mrs. Di.
Welcome!
My laptop is power off.
I have emails to reply to.
Is there an outlet I could use?
Go to the study.
Charge it there.
Thanks.
(Amber Perfume)
(They are)
(the new hires from marketing.)
(Vibrant,)
(energetic,)
(and great at pleasing people.)
Mrs. Di.
- Hello, Mrs. Di. - Hello!
Hello.
(Yu Meng,)
(stay calm.)
(Do you really think)
(every smart, attractive woman)
(has their eye on your husband?)
Hi again, Meng.
I was going over contracts
with your company,
and they brought me along.
So here I am.
I hope you don't mind.
Of course not.
Welcome!
(Amber Perfume)
Come.
I only heard today
that you worked at Jiali,
and you helped a lot
for its success today.
I was pretty surprised.
I had no idea
you were so capable before.
That's all in the past.
Weng Yue.
Honey,
the hand cream ran out,
and I haven't replaced it yet.
You have to put lotion on wet hands,
or the wind will dry them out.
Mr. Di,
you really dote on your wife!
I'm so jealous of her.
She's so lucky.
I'm so envious.
I hope you find
a boyfriend like that.
Ma'am,
is Mr. Di here?
I need his signature
on this document,
but he didn't reply
on WeChat.
=The Vanishing Beauty= (Next Episode Preview)
It's your wife's lipstick.
Does it look good?
(I'm Jiao Xu) Does the offer still stand?
Of course.
I wanted to go to Dongji Island too.
I thought you went there
and was going to ask
how it was.
Mr. Di.
Meng wanted duck soup with bamboo shoots.
I'll add some cordyceps.
I heard Dongji Island
is a place you go with a partner.
Were you with yours?
I'd waited for her
to come to me.
And today,
she did.
♪How to balance♪
♪Lessons never taught♪
♪If choices must be made♪
♪I'll hold onto my innocence♪
♪I was never the clever one♪
♪Just trying to live with heart♪
♪To love, to hate, to seek a more genuine soul♪
♪Some embrace while some turn cold♪
♪The ones who stay are the sincerest♪
♪We cannot let go♪
♪I was never the clever one♪
♪Just trying to live with heart♪
♪To love, to hate, to seek a more genuine soul♪
♪Some embrace while some turn cold♪
♪The ones who stay are the sincerest♪
♪We cannot let go♪